vestedbb.com 2014-05-26

# Business for Sale-Buy a Business-Privacy Policy-VESTED BUSINESS BROKERS

_**NOTICE**_

\- This Web Site collects certain information relative to users who visit the site. 

In some cases, our company obtains information that personally identifies the visitors to our web site. However, it is not our policy to sell or otherwise provide access to such information to unaffiliated third parties. 

## Category I

\- Information on users who visit our site to read or download information on our pages. From these users, we collect and store the following information: 

      1\. The domain name through which you gained access to our Web site;  
      2\. The precise time and date that you entered our web site.  
      3\. The URL of the web page through which you linked to our web site. 

## Category II

\- Users who send us e-mails, faxes, or fill-in online forms containing personal information that identifies the visitor. Any information or personal data that we collect in this way is used, solely, for purposes related to the Brokerage Services we provide to our Business Owners. Specifically, they have asked us to find Qualified Buyers for their existing businesses and to do so we must obtain demographic and financial information from these individuals. We do not sell this information to third parties. 

Any information that we collect as part of our stated business practices is used to identify demographic preferences, key areas of business interest, and to provide a legal standing with regard to confidentiality and compliance with the terms of our business agreements and services. Certain other information may be gathered while you are accessing various sections of our site to help us determine which content and business listings are of greater interest to our visitors. We may also use such information in statistical form to assist us in business and marketing strategies and programs. We utilize software programs to create summary statistics, which we utilize for the above purposes.WE WILL NOT SELL OR SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH ANY OTHER PARTIES. 

As a security measure for ourselves and our users, we utilize certain software programs to monitor traffic to our site and within our network. This software also enables us to identify unauthorized upload attempts, access to our system, and other attempts to cause damage to our systems. 

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Vested Business Brokers, LTD. If there are any change to our privacy policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this page and notify you of these changes by email. If you need to contact us about any of these policies, please send an email to 

[_operations@vestedbb.com_](mailto:operations@vestedbb.com) and we will route your inquiry to the proper recipient(s). 

If, at any time, you wish to unsubscribe to our email notices, you may send a message to [_operations@vestedbb.com_](mailto:operations@vestedbb.com) with UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line, or you can use the unsubscribe link on the bottom of any of our business announcements.  You may also send your request to Vested Business Brokers, Ltd., 50 Karl Avenue, Smithtown, NY 11787, or by calling **877-735-5224**.
